漫威电视出品
好  这样吧  给他上三副铐
All right, here's the plan. Triple-cuff him.
一队  负责押送
Alpha team, you take point positions in the convoy.
二队断后
Bravo team will bring up the rear.
记住  我们可以开火
Remember, we're clear to engage,
如果他眼神有点不对  就来上一枪
so if he so much as looks at you funny, light him up.
收到
Copy that.
听到了吗  疯子  我有特别为你准备的东西
You hear that, freak? I got something special for you.
没必要这样
This isn't necessary.
有必要
Yeah, it is.
不行  你得让我们处理好  奈特小姐
No. You need to let us finish. Ms. Knight. Ms. Knight!
是奈特警官  我没事
It's Detective Knight, and I'm fine.
我想和凯奇谈谈
I need a moment with Cage.
米丝蒂  我们有特殊命令
Misty, we have special orders.
马里奥  别这样
Mario, come on.
我刚被人挟持
I was just held hostage.
我只想跟他谈谈
I just need a minute with him.
我们会在这里  有我们在
All right. We'll be right here. We got your back.
安全
Clear!
你完蛋了
You going down.
也是时候了
It's about damn time.
水腹蛇  阿尔比尼警官  还有这里发生的事
Cottonmouth, Officer Albini, what just popped off in there...
你朋友逃走了
Look, your friend is in the wind.
他们现在铐上了头号公敌
They've got public enemy number one in handcuffs
让世界看到
for the whole world to see...
这样他们就不用去找别人了
so they're not looking for anybody else.
护送你的警官都配有改良版犹大子弹
Every officer in your detail has those modified Judas bullets.
换我是你  在抵达警局之前
I wouldn't try anything if I were you...
可不会耍什么花招
before I got to the precinct.
你没有那么疯狂吧
You're not that crazy, are you?
一向没有
Always.
把他送去监狱
Take his ass to jail.
走吧
Come on.
我们走  上路
All right, let's go. We're rolling.
三副手铐  是不是有点过分了
Three sets of cuffs? Isn't that overkill?
有相机呢  我们得装出一副尽在掌控中的样子
The camera's on. We need to look like we're in control.
这押送烂透了
It's a shit detail.
你还以为紧急情况小队的人
You'd think ESU would be in the back
会在后面拿着枪指着他呢
with those guns pointed at him.
我们也有同样的枪和子弹
We've got the same guns and bullets they do.
我妻子说会出现他这种人
You know, my wife says it's the end of days,
是因为要世界末日了
people like him popping up.
自从夏娃咬了苹果后她们就一直这么说
They've been saying that since Eve bit the apple.
凯奇是进化了
Cage? He's evolution.
不管他是什么  都很可怕
Whatever he is, it's just scary.
让我感觉自己很渺小  无礼
Makes me feel small. Insignificant.
不安全感
Insecure?
他们经常说  只要你是黑人  就回不了头
You know what they say. Once you go black, you never go back.
至少我妻子经常和我这么说
At least that's what your wife keeps telling me.
她回家的时候我早就睡着了
I was fast asleep when she came home.
你女儿老是搞得我很累
Your daughter already wore me out.
坐稳了
Just sit tight.
该死
God damn it.
流浪老太  就不能让她挪边上去吗
Homeless lady. Can't they move her out of the way?
你阻碍了警方押运
You are in the path of a police convoy.
请马上让开
Clear the road immediately.
快
Come on!
凯奇逃跑了  开火
Cage must not escape. Fire at will!
快快快
Go, go, go, go, go!
他往南边跑了
He went down the south side.
谁给我汇报一下情况
Somebody give me a sitrep right now!
二队  上  上
Team two... Let's go, let's go!
年轻的警察总是喜欢追着人跑
Young cops always wanna chase somebody.
我呢  更喜欢在人家会去的地方等着
Me, I'd rather be where they're already going.
他们告诉我犹大能干掉你这样的人
They told us these Judas bullets can kill someone like you.
你不想死吗  那就别跑
You don't want to die? Don't run.
我宁死也不要回到监狱
I'd rather die than go back to prison.
不自由毋宁死
Live free or die?
你想来新汉普顿这一套
You wanna get all New Hampshire about this shit?
我没意见
Fine with me.
-警察杀手人人喊打  -我没有杀警察
- Cop killers don't survive these streets. - I didn't kill a cop.
我跟你或你们没有过节
My problem isn't with you or yours.
我有更大的问题要担心
It's much bigger than that.
有人因为你的所作所为而称你为英雄
Some people are calling you a hero for what you did.
在康妮家  老爹的店
Connie's, Pop's...
我不是英雄
I'm no hero.
但我的确要干掉要为这一切负责的人
But I do need to take out the person responsible for all this.
你不认识我了吧
You don't recognize me, do you?
你在老爹的店见过你
I've seen you at Pop's before.
老爹剪了我12年的头发
Pop cut my hair for 12 years.
他也不觉得自己是英雄
He didn't think he was a hero, either.
他只是在做了几年错事后想要弥补
He was just trying to do some right after years of wrong.
我希望我对你的看法没错
I hope I'm right about you.
支持你的人比你想象中的要多
More people rooting for you than you think.
-你要怎么告诉你的同僚  -实话实说
- What are you gonna tell your people? - The truth.
我看到你了  但你甩掉了我
I had you in my sights, but you outran me.
我老了
I'm getting old.
卢克
Luke?
你最好抓住那个狡猾的混蛋
You better catch that slippery son of a bitch.
第一季  第十二集
卢克凯奇
哈莱姆天堂发生惨剧后
Moments after the tumultuous events at Harlem's Paradise,
重大新闻
当局通缉逃犯卢克·凯奇
哈莱姆天堂发生惨剧后
Moments after the tumultuous events at Harlem's Paradise,
重大新闻
当局通缉逃犯卢克·凯奇
据传杀害警察的逃犯
fugitive and alleged cop killer
重大新闻
当局通缉逃犯卢克·凯奇
卢克·凯奇被带上手铐押走
Luke Cage was brought out in handcuffs.
重大新闻
当局通缉逃犯卢克·凯奇
现在  市里最...
And now the city's most...
重大新闻
当局通缉逃犯卢克·凯奇
现在  市里最...
And now the city's most...
很高兴你打给我  威利斯
Hey, I'm glad you called me, Willis.
卢克·凯奇在逃  沙兹在他们手里
Luke Cage is on the run. They got Shades in bracelets,
但是他们过不了多久就会查到你头上  哥们儿
but they're gonna be onto you before long, brother.
你最好知道
Best believe that.
赶紧消失  把现金盘了  才是你最好的选择
Getting ghost and liquidizing your cash, that was the right move.
必须谨慎对待卢克·凯奇...
Luke Cage must be approached with...
换我可不会乱碰
I wouldn't touch any of that.
一般人不会一而再测试我的耐性
People don't test me more than once.
我明白
I overstand.
你想让我干什么
What you need me for?
我知道你是一个有判断和品位的男人
I understand you're a man of discretion and taste
并且有大量对我商品有兴趣的买家人脉
with numerous connections willing to pay full price for my wares.
我仍然可以东山再起
I can still collect from the shadows.
-坏消息  响尾蛇  -把墨镜摘了
- Bad news, Diamondback. - Take those off!
我去了你的房间  你的档案都不见了
I went to your crib. The files you had are gone.
你是我的人  不是吗
I had you, didn't I?
完全同意
I couldn't resist.
我喜欢你  奇普
I like you, Zip.
你有雄心壮志  这让你前途无量
You've got ambition. It'll take you far...
但是你要做你该做的事
as long as you stay in your place.
权力的48条法则第一条
The first of the 48 laws of power.
做人要低调
Never outshine the master.
沙兹就犯过这种错误
That was the mistake Shades made.
他质疑我  他怀疑我  他想自己单干
He questioned me. He doubted me. He tried to reach too far.
他想成为伊卡洛斯那种人
He was on some Icarus shit.
你知道那是谁吗
Do you know who that is?
-知道  他和肯德里克写了一首诗  -不
- Yeah, he had a verse with Kendrick. Right? - No...
伊卡洛斯是一个戴着假翅膀飞向太阳的孩子
Icarus was the boy who flew too close to the sun with fake wings.
沙兹不是问题  他还在被拘禁
Shades is no problem. He's still in custody.
马上就不是了
Not for long.
你要把监狱炸掉吗
You gonna blow the joint up?
不  他马上要被保释出来了
No, he's going to be bailed out.
为什么  这没有道理
The hell for? That don't make no sense!
看到了吗  这就是质疑
See? The questioning.
一切从此开始
That's how it starts.
我需要一个助手
I'm gonna have an opening.
你要来吗
You gonna step up?
我愿意为你马首是瞻
I'm down to do whatever you need.
-没有问题  -好孩子
- No problem. - Good boy.
你愿意吗
So are you down?
我愿意
I'm down.
只要有买卖做  我就没问题
As long as the business is business, I'm good with it.
没有买卖  恕不奉陪
Till then, I'm out of here, man.
奇普  给特科展示一下
Show Turk out, Zip.
这位罗密欧是在阴间也是可以呼风唤雨的人
Romeo would roll over in his grave,
你不过只是在小猫小狗面前耍耍花枪
the way you hop-skipping with these cats nowadays.
他是个道上的真爷们  你只是个孩子
He was a man on these streets. You's a boy.
你他妈在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
你和我一样  就是看中了他的钱
You're down here in his pocket, same as me.
是的  我在和他做生意
I'm doing business with him, yes.
但我不是他的手下  更不是他的走狗
But I ain't his boy. And I definitely ain't his bitch.
这些老头子只会胡言乱语
These old-ass niggas talkin' about shit
他们什么都不知道
they don't even know about.
箱子里有什么
So... what's in the box?
有七宗罪之一  我的孩子
One of the seven deadly sins, my boy...
我要把它宣泄在我的老朋友卡尔身上
which I plan to unleash on dear old Carl.
哪一宗呢
Which one?
愤怒
Wrath.
我们需要处理响尾蛇
欧内斯托是对的  多明戈  现在是绝佳的机会
我们有实力
况且在古巴  牙买加  多米尼加和海地的领袖死了的情况下
我们将拥有毒品  枪支  所有的一切
一跃称王
他把他们全部干掉时我就在场
I was there when he took them all out.
我就在隔壁
Right next door.
我们有毒品
We got the drugs.
我们有钱
We got that money.
但是我们有了枪  就控制了一切
But with the guns, we can control everything.
这里  那些岛屿  以及南方
Here, the islands, further south...
我们将所向披靡
We'd be unstoppable.
所以你有什么计划
我们把他救出来
We take him out.
我们去夺回属于我们的一切
We go after what's ours.
我们去找响尾蛇
Let's go find Diamondback.
纽约警署
阿尔瓦雷斯·埃尔南
面向照相机
Turn and face the camera.
纽约警署
阿尔瓦雷斯·埃尔南
好了  下一个
All right, let's go. Move it.
你应该在医院的
You're supposed to be in the hospital.
太急着拼命只会让
Push yourself too hard too soon
一切变得更糟
and you could make it worse, you know.
-谢谢你的关心  -你一点都不领情
- I appreciate your concern. - No, you don't.
我需要一个彻底健康的你
I need you at 100%.
我要证明卢克·凯奇是无辜的
I need to prove Luke Cage is innocent.
人质都一直坚持
Well, the hostages have all been consistent
卢克·凯奇从来没有用枪指着他们
that Luke Cage never held them at gunpoint.
他中了圈套  你知道的  普莉希拉
He was set up. You know it, Priscilla.
警察局一半的人都他妈知道
Half this damn department knows it.
我们需要追查威利斯·斯崔克
We need to be going after Willis Stryker.
那么为什么卢克·凯奇逃跑了
Well, then why is Luke Cage running?
他一个黑人  被持有特殊子弹的警察
He's a black man being chased by the cops...
到处追捕
oh, with special bullets.
被指控谋杀警察
Accused of killing a cop,
你还问他为什么逃跑吗  拜托
and you're asking why he's running? Come on.
看看阿尔瓦雷斯·"沙兹"·埃尔南多么惬意
Look at how relaxed Hernan "Shades" Alvarez is.
他知道他哪里都不会去的
He knows he's not going anywhere anytime soon,
所以怡然自得
so he's resting up.
他知道他是有罪的
He knows he's guilty.
看到这名罪犯了吗
See this perp?
看他在抖腿  说明他紧张
Look how his foot is bouncing. Nervous.
难怪他的诨号是"糖糖"
No wonder his street name is Sugar.
我都不用问他  就能知道很多信息
I don't even have to say a word, and here come the waterworks.
他很有可能是无辜的
He's probably innocent...
或者和他要供出的人比就是个小卒
or less guilty than whoever he's about to give up.
这水平堪比警探老婆
That's a detectives' wives' tale.
你不能通过这个就判定是否有罪
You can't prove guilt or innocence by that.
但是你可以
Oh, but you can...
-因为卢克向你承诺过了  -卢克
- because Luke gave you his word. - Luke--
现在他的行为比他的承诺更有说服力
Right now, his actions are speaking louder than his words.
卢克·凯奇
Luke Cage...
救了我的命
saved my life.
我从不质疑我们是否应该追捕响尾蛇
I don't dispute that we should be bringing in Diamondback,
但是为了真相大白  我们应该把两个人都带回来
but to get to the truth, we need to bring them both in.
好吧  让我把话说在前面
Okay, well, let me lead the charge.
一定要确保卢克被安全地带回来
Make sure Luke is brought in safely.
他跳出押运车的时候就已经失去机会了
He threw away his chance when he jumped out that damn van.
现在正像市长期望的那样
Now they will shoot him on sight
警察一看到他就会开枪
with the mayor's blessing.
你知道吗  至少让我审一下沙兹
You know what? At least let me take a crack at Shades.
他和所有人都关系匪浅
He's in deep with all the players.
他吓不到我
He doesn't scare me.
-警探  -我能解决他
- Detective-- - I can handle him.
你刚刚被枪击
You just got shot.
我想要你回家  休息一下
I need you to go home, get some rest.
我来审沙兹
I'll interview Shades.
我祖母非常喜欢哈莱姆天堂
My grandmother loved Harlem's Paradise.
她处理这里的每一个细节
She took care of all the small details.
她爱着它
She loved it.
从壁画
From the murals...
玻璃工艺品  一直到桌布和餐巾
the glasswork, all the way down to the table linens.
不忽视任何细节
No fine point was overlooked.
这是她的遗产
This was her legacy.
我的家族现在声名狼藉
My family's in tatters,
都是因为响尾蛇  见鬼
and it's all because of Diamondback. Shit!
我知道  我知道
I know, I know...
我知道我得走出这里
I need to get out in front of this.
发表一篇声明关于达蒙·布恩的声明
Release a statement about Damon Boone
以示尊重
and how much I respected him.
这不是我想说的
That is not what I was gonna say.
只是  拜托  别再演讲了
Well, yeah, just-- Please, no lectures.
这只是一个房子
This is just a thing.
房子可以重新盖  当你盖好的时候
Things can be rebuilt, and when you do,
它就是你的遗产了
you rebuild it as your legacy.
不只是酒吧
Not just the clubs.
我想真正参与进来
I want to be a part of that.
我是这样想的
Here's what I think.
控制舆论是重中之重
Controlling the narrative is everything.
我们不能有任何的潜在威胁
We can't have any loose threads.
所以任何可能在这里听到
So anyone who might have overheard
你和响尾蛇以及沙兹对话的人
anything you said to Diamondback or Shades in here...
都是威胁
is a threat.
完全正确
You're absolutely correct.
我能为你做点什么
How may I be of service?
我不想你惹上任何的麻烦
I wouldn't want you to do anything untoward.
绝对不会
Never.
好的
Okay.
我没时间管这个
I don't have time for this.
不要动
Don't move.
他会打爆你的头  他已经疯了
He'll blow your head off. He's crazy like that.
别想着反抗
Don't try no shit.
我的错  麦斯  我听着武当故事长大的
My bad, Meth. I grew up on that Wu-Tang shit.
-但是你知道那感觉的  -你还是认真的吗
- But you know how it is. - Are you serious?
你真的想这时候和我谈吗
Are you really trying to have a conversation right now?
我只是想说  你是一个...
I'm just tryin'... I'm just sayin'... You're the man...
戴上面具
Pull your mask down!
你应该去看门的  布莱斯
You supposed to be watchin' the damn door, Bryce!
叫我真名的事情上我是怎么说的  迈克尔
What I say about using my government name, Michael?
见鬼  伙计
Damn, homie.
你看起来像从乳酪磨碎器里走出来的
You look like you went through a cheese grater.
天哪  你是卢克
Oh, snap, you Luke--
我不是故意的
I ain't mean that.
把你的电话给我
Give me your phone.
电话  蠢货
The phone, fool.
我的错  伙计
Yo, my bad, man.
你知道的  看你把我伙计打飞的时候
You know, I just got a little nervous and shit
我有点紧张
when you threw my mans across the-- -
是你
It's you.
对  就是你
Yeah, it's you.
不  伙计  是你啊
No, man, it's you.
我以前特别喜欢《PLO风格》
Yo, man, "P.L.O. Style" was my joint back in the day.
耶稣上帝啊
Sweet Christmas.
伙计 等一下
Yeah, man, one second.
是我
Hey. It's me.
他们会找我
Yeah, they'll be looking for me.
我会小心活动  过会见你
I'll lay in the cut. I'll see you in a few.
你是加大码的吗
You a double XL?
早就想到了  伙计
Way ahead of you, homie,
给警察打电话
Call the cops.
我认识很多人
I know a lot of people
愿意出钱保护你
who would pay you for this kind of protection.
钱他们可以留着
They can keep their money.
再见
Salute.
你之前见过这种事情吗
You ever see anything like that before?
哈莱姆  小子
Harlem, baby.
这就是哈莱姆
Harlem.
-你好  -奈特警探
- Hello? - Detective Knight?
-坎迪斯  -是我
- Candace? - Yeah.
这是谁的号码
What number are you calling me from?
我从便利店买的预付费电话
A prepaid phone I picked up from CVS.
我要见你一面
I need to see you.
-来分局  -不行  不行
- Come into the precinct. - No. No.
你见过玛莉娅找到那个律师
You saw how quickly Mariah sent that lawyer
把我弄出去有多快
and got me out of there.
你之前不想和我谈的
You didn't wanna talk to me before.
是什么让你现在相信我了
What makes you trust me now?
因为卢克·凯奇的所作所为
Because Luke Cage does.
他救了我  你也看穿我了
He saved my life. And you saw right through me.
-你想知道真相  对吗  -你在哪里
- You want the truth, right? - Where are you?
-听着  如果你帮不上忙  -坎迪斯
- Look, if you can't help... - Candace.
告诉我一个地址  我会过去
Tell me a place, and I will be there.
你本该去雷克斯的  但我把你留下
You should be at Rikers right now, but I held you...
因为我觉得你有话要说
because I think you have something to say.
律师
Lawyer.
我看过你的记录  阿尔瓦雷斯先生
I know your record, Mr. Alvarez.
90年代末的时候来到哈莱姆
Came up in Harlem,
一直跟着水腹蛇
rolled around with Cottonmouth in the late '90s,
在斯波福德和纽约州新新监狱待过
spent some time at Spofford, Sing Sing,
然后你犯了大事  被送去海门监狱
then you made it to the big time, went to Seagate.
律师
Lawyer.
康奈尔·斯托克斯死了  但你却还活着
Cornell Stokes is dead, but you're still alive.
我从没见过这么快的传讯
And I've never seen an arraignment happen so quickly.
200万美元的保释金
Two million dollar bail...
还是有人付的现金
and someone paid it in cash.
谁是你的新赞助人  是威利斯·斯崔克吗
Who's your new sponsor? Is it Willis Stryker?
我要
Law...
律师
...yer.
你涉及劫持人质事件  埃尔南
You were part of a hostage situation, Hernan.
即便你的律师真能把你弄出去
Even if your lawyer does get you out...
你也跑不了
you won't be walking away from that.
你将面临多起绑架和持械的起诉
That's multiple kidnapping and weapons charges.
25年监禁听起来这么样  最少这个数
How does 25 years to life sound to you? Minimum.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
真的
Yep.
好吧
Okay.
我当时在俱乐部
I... I was in the club.
我看到发生了什么
I saw what happened.
我知道是谁干的
I know who did it.
好
Okay.
我们可以保护你  但我要一个能核实的名字
We can protect you, but I need a name to verify.
是谁
Who was it?
是斯崔克吗
Was it Stryker?
他的名字是
He goes by...
律师
lawyer.
要我拼出来吗
You need me to spell it?
-你管这叫安全  -这里很空旷
- You call this safe? - We're hiding in plain sight.
我罩着你呢  暂时而已
I've got you. For now.
坎迪斯  再骗我一次
Lie to me again, Candace,
我就离开  你就只能靠你自己了
I walk away from here, and you are on your own.
-这可不是胡扯的  -等着瞧吧
- It's not bullshit. - We'll see.
你怎么离开哈莱姆天堂的
How did you even get out of Harlem's Paradise
居然没人拦你
without being stopped?
他们忙着逮捕卢克  我就直接走了
They were so busy trying to arrest Luke, I just walked away.
到底什么事
So what is it?
你要告诉我什么重要的事
What do you need to tell me that's so important?
水腹蛇死的那晚我在俱乐部
I was at the club the night Cottonmouth died.
我已经知道了
I already know that.
我是说就在他死后
I mean right after.
玛莉娅杀了他
Mariah killed him.
你身上的衣服扔到垃圾袋里
The trash bag is for the clothes you're wearing now.
所有衣服都扔掉  包括珠宝
Every stitch goes in. Jewelry, too.
斯珀洛克会把它们烧掉
Someone from Spurlock's will incinerate them.
好谎言的秘诀就是
The secret to any good lie
要跟真相没有交集
is it has to run parallel to the truth.
你怎么知道的
How do you know this?
他们说话的时候我听到了
I heard them talking about it.
照我说的做
Do what I say.
那个总戴着墨镜的人  他也在场
The guy who always wears sunglasses, he was there.
栽赃卢克·凯奇杀了水腹蛇是他的主意
It was his idea to say Luke Cage killed Cottonmouth.
我吓坏了
I was so scared.
我溜了出去  回到了储物柜那边
I snuck out of there, back to the lockers.
我试着冷静下来
And, um, I was trying to calm myself down.
我上去后  戴眼镜那人
When I went upstairs, the guy with the glasses
给我了五万块让我说个故事
offered me $50,000 to tell a story.
所以我就说了
So I told one.
-你现在为何要承认  -因为我良心过不去
- Why are you coming clean now? - 'Cause I can't live with this.
尤其是卢克还救了我的命
Especially after Luke saving my life.
如果你们能保证我的安全
If you can guarantee my safety,
我愿意作证把刚才说的再说一次
I will testify about everything I just told you.
玛莉娅比水腹蛇更让我害怕
Mariah scares me more than Cottonmouth.
我问过她是否觉得是卢克干的
I asked her if she thought Luke did it,
主要想看看我能不能信任她
mostly to see if I could trust her.
想看看她会不会跟我说实话
To see if she would tell me the truth.
她直视着我的眼睛  说
She looked me right in my eye and said...
"你永远不知道一个人能做出什么事"
"You never know what anyone is capable of."
重点是她说那话的语气
It was the way she said it.
要是她知道我跟你聊过  她会杀了我
She... she would kill me if she knew I was speaking to you.
我真的相信她会
I truly believe that.
谢谢你肯帮我
Thank you for helping me.
我会钉死玛莉娅·迪拉德的
I'm gonna nail Mariah Dillard's ass to the wall.
-还有谁知道你来了  -只有我朋友莱斯利
- Who else knows that you're here? - Just my friend Leslie.
别打给任何人  包括莱斯利
Don't call anyone else, not even Leslie.
不行  把你的电话给我
As a matter of fact, give me your phone.
快点
Come on.
好吧  这是我在路上买的
Okay. Now, I picked this up...
以防万一
on the way, just in case.
我已经把我的电话输进去了
It's already got my number programed in there,
如果我打来或者发短信  你会知道是我
so if I call or text, you know it's me.
你的胳膊还好吗
Is your arm okay?
我扣扳机的手指没问题
My trigger finger is just fine.
走吧  我们走
Come on, let's go.
-去哪  -索莱达家
- Where? - Soledad's.
她女儿克莱尔
Her daughter Claire
就是在哈莱姆天堂帮你治疗脚踝的人
is the one who treated your ankle at Harlem's Paradise.
她也在那里
She'll be there, too.
我亲自送你过去
I'm gonna take you there myself.
不骗你  当时子弹满天飞
No lie. Bullets was flying everywhere and shit.
你想告诉我
You trying to tell me
这些是弹孔吗
that those are bullet holes?
麦斯  我爱你  但麻烦你赶紧滚
Man, Meth, I love you, but get out of here.
我不相信
I... I don't believe that.
HB  我之前也跟你想得一样
HB, I thought the same thing...
直到那矮个子开了枪  打中了凯奇两枪
until shorty pulled the biscuit and let two off on Cage
结果弹飞了
and they bounced off.
子弹就那么弹开了
Bullets ricochetin' and shit.
听着  我说的是实话
Look, I'm telling y'all the truth.
我看到你们的表情了  你们不信
I see y'all over there, y'all don't believe it.
相信我  是真的
Trust me, it's the truth.
他把这些哥们的枪打掉后
And after he smacked fire out these dudes,
他留下了帽衫  让我和戈麦斯报警
he left the hoodie, told me and Gomez to call the police.
你知道我不会报警的  然后他就走了
You know I ain't calling no po-po. Then he bounced.
-说你保证  -我保证  真的  我跟你说
- Say word. - Word, Sway. I'm telling you.
他甚至把那人的枪卷成了球  就像手工作业
He even balled the dude's gun up like some old homework.
但我的问题是  如果他是无辜的
But my thing is, though, if he innocent,
那为什么要逃跑
so what he running for?
刀枪不入几乎跟身为黑人一样容易被误解
Bulletproof always gonna come second to being black.
HB  你该知道的  你是泽西州的  泽西啊
HB, you should know that. You from Jers. Jers!
看来他对你的出身很吃惊啊
Sound like he stunted on you right there.
他惊呆了  真的惊呆了  真的
He did stunt. It was a stunt. It was a stunt.
你为什么对我惊呆了
Why you gotta stunt on me? -
不  我是说真的
No, I mean, seriously.
说真的  我是说  如果是我...
Seriously, though, what I'm just saying, like, if that was me...
-对  -我在逃亡
- Right. - And I was on the run.
为什么还要插手
Why even get involved?
但他还是站出来了
But he did.
那些家伙可紧张了  任何事都有可能发生
And those dudes was nervous, so anything could've happened.
在我看来  卢克·凯奇救了我的命
As far as I'm concerned, Luke Cage saved my life, man.
就是这样  伙计
That's what's up, man.
我觉得他可不像什么杀警察的人
You know what, that don't sound like no cop killer to me.
真的  真的
For real, for real.
看到一个黑人  刀枪不入
You know, there's somethin' powerful about seeing a black man
无所畏惧是很有冲击力的事
that's bulletproof and unafraid.
-你们知道吗  -是啊  是啊
- Come on, y'all. You know? - Yeah, yeah.
街头大爱凯奇
Streets got mad love for Cage.
我也大爱凯奇  他是我们的人
I got mad love for Cage, man, and... and he one of ours.
是啊  但你知道吗
Yeah, yeah. But you know what?
我们也大爱你
We got mad love for you, too.
-绝对的  -你也是我们的人
- No doubt. - You one of ours, man.
节目快结束了  你要给我们来几句吗
You know, the show's almost over, man. You gonna spit for us?
-当然了  -他要来几句了
- Of course. - Oh, man! He 'bout to spit!
听众们  迎接听觉盛宴吧
Citizens, you are in for a treat.
最好的歌手之一  唯一的马瑟曼
One of the best to pick up the mic, the one and only Method Man!
准备好了吗
Hey, yo, Sway. You all ready?
我要将这首歌
I'mma dedicate this one to
献给街头最强壮的猛汉
the hardest individual on the street right now.
卢克·凯奇  你早就知道了
Luke Cage, you already know.
"刀枪不入的爱"  哥们  开始吧
"Bulletproof Love" Your way, brother. Let's get it.
听好了
Listen.
*Man, it is what it is*
*Can't understand a man If you ain't lived what he lived*
*Roaches in the crib Ain't got no food up in the fridge*
*Plus the crime runnin' rampant And it's screwin' up the kids*
*Sway, admit What kind of paradise is this?*
*I just want my 40 acres And some carats on the wrist*
*But these snakes Is tryin' to gather in the pit*
*Where you get a cottonmouth Pluckin' ashes off the clip*
*Off the rip, now a challenger exists*
*And he bulletproof, shoot What kinda caliber is this?*
*Got thugs in the store With the barrel on your lips*
*Sayin', "Empty out the drawer"
*Before he pound you with the grip*
*Lord, who to call When no one obeys the law*
*And there ain't no Iron Man That can come and save us all?*
*Power to the people And Luke Cage the cause*
*And the cops got it wrong We don't think Cage involved*
* Look, dog, a hero, never had one*
* Already took Malcolm and Martin This is the last one*
* I beg your pardon Somebody pullin' a fast one*
*Now we got a hero for hire And he a black one*
*And bullet-hole hoodies Is the fashion*
*We in Harlem's Paradise Tell the Captain*
*That I'm about to trade the mic For a Magnum*
* Give up my life For Trayvon to have one*
* Yeah, 'cause this is bulletproof love*
* And you already know What a bulletproof does*
*So you can take it From a bulletproof thug*
* The hood got his back, dog Bulletproof love*
* Blood thicker than mud*
*And who am I to judge If you get a gun in the club?*
* 'Cause you already know What a bulletproof does*
*When the hood got your back, dog Bulletproof love *
为了老爹  安息吧  兄弟
Shout out to Pop. RIP, my brother.
街头已经疯了  你知道我在说什么
The streets is crazy right now, you know what I'm sayin'?
人们说我们不再需要英雄了  但现在你出现了
People say we don't need another hero, but now we got one.
不管你喜不喜欢  卢克·凯奇  请相信
Whether you like it or not, Luke Cage, please believe it, sir,
街头是你的后盾
the streets got your back.
你已经有刀枪不入的爱  宝贝
You're already bulletproof love, baby!
真洗脑  这里是《摇摆大学》
Yeah! That was dope. You got it right here on Sway's Universe.
马瑟曼哥们  HB和刀枪不入的爱  卢克·凯奇
The homie, Method Man, HB, and the bulletproof thug, Luke Cage.
执法部门全力搜索卢克·凯奇
Law enforcement is in a frenzy looking for Luke Cage.
街头出现很多假冒者
There have been numerous false sightings,
有些人穿着带弹孔的连帽衫
with some people wearing hoodies with holes
弹孔英雄
有些人穿着带弹孔的连帽衫
with some people wearing hoodies with holes
从而声援这名罪犯
as a sign of solidarity with
弹孔英雄
很多人仍然认为他是一名英雄
an outlaw some people still perceive to be a hero.
弹孔英雄
清晨摇摆  有什么话要说  朋友
Sway in the Morning. What's on your mind, citizen?
我还记得当年拉瑞·戴维斯逃亡的时候
Yo, I remember when Larry Davis was on the run back in the day.
警察到处找他  因为他们
Cops came at him 'cause they were just as corrupt,
跟他一样腐败  危险  肮脏
dangerous and jacked up as he was.
老爹理发店
跟他一样腐败  危险  肮脏
dangerous and jacked up as he was.
我真的觉得我们现在
I don't think we're getting
老爹理发店
并不清楚卢克·凯奇事件的全貌
the full story on Luke Cage yet, for real.
老爹理发店
并不清楚卢克·凯奇事件的全貌
the full story on Luke Cage yet, for real.
我可不会信政府这一套
I wouldn't put it past the government, man.
我们会为你们寻找答案
You know, we're gonna be searching for the answers for you,
我们一得知真相
and once we get the facts,
就会在《摇摆大学》中公布
we're gonna put it right here on Sway's Universe, all right?
谢谢你们的来电  又有人打进来了
Thanks for your call, citizen. We got another person on the line.
快点
Now. Come on! All right.
得了吧  你们知道他不在这里
Oh, come on, man. You know he's not here.
和电脑玩我还能理解
I understand playing against the computer,
但你要怎么打败你自己呢
but, um, how do you beat yourself?
象棋讲究预知
Chess is a game of anticipation.
如果你知道每一种可能的走法
If you know every single possible move,
你能抢在你对手之前预知他的下法
you can anticipate your adversary's next move before he does.
真深奥
That's deep.
如果我们发现你藏匿他  你可吃不了兜着走
If we find out you've been hiding him, there'll be hell to pay.
出去的时候不要弄断
Yeah, well, just don't break the hinges
门上的铰链
on that door on your way out.
我才刚修好
I just got it fixed.
真是惊险[剃得不好]
That was a close shave.
这双关真差
Bad pun.
你到底为什么要回来
What the hell did you even come back for, man?
我必须回来
I had to.
为了哈莱姆
For Harlem.
我得在响尾蛇毁掉大家的家园前除掉他
Take care of Diamondback before he made it bad for everybody.
忘了哈莱姆  忘了你哥
Well, forget Harlem. Forget your brother!
你和一个那么漂亮的女人坐上新车上了路
You're on the road in a brand new car and a woman that fine?
你还刀枪不入
And you're bulletproof.
我要是你就永不现身
You'd have never seen my black ass again.
偶尔抢个银行  永不回头
I'd rob the occasional bank and never look back.
城里所有的警察都在找你  伙计
You got every cop in the city looking for you, brother.
黑鬼们还在写什么卢克·凯奇的叙事歌
Negroes writing Luke Cage ballads and shit.
你是怎么打算的
So... what's the plan?
把所有玩家都围起来
To box in all the players.
好吧
Well...
沙兹进了监狱
Shades is in jail.
玛莉娅是自由身  但她可不会站在你这边
Mariah's out, but she ain't exactly on your side.
你可以跟踪他们两个
Now you could tail both of 'em,
但不知道要等上多久
but no telling how long
他们才会把你引到你的猎物那
that'll take for them to lead you to your prey.
米丝蒂呢
What about Misty?
不行  她已经自顾不暇了
No, she's got her hands full already.
她一边试着在分局帮我洗清罪名
She's trying to clear my name inside the precinct
一边试着抓我进去
and bring me in at the same time.
我们得小心应对她
We gotta be careful with her.
那你只剩下一个选择了
That leaves you one other option.
另找一个能找到响尾蛇的人
Someone else to find Diamondback.
给
Here.
特科
Turk.
特科或许是个小卒  但他不蠢
Turk may be a pawn, but he's not dumb.
如果他认为自己被算计了就会消失
If he thinks he's being set up, he'll disappear.
这你就交给我吧
You let me worry about that.
特科  是我  波比
Hey, Turk, it's Bobby.
我或许能搞到
Listen, I might be able to get my hands
差不多30双乔丹球鞋
on about 30 pairs of Jordans.
是老款的飞人乔丹五代球鞋
They're the vintage Air Jordan 5s.
你就当我是大街上捡的吧
Let's just say they fell off the back of a truck.
好  什么时候
Okay, when?
这是谁
Who's this?
姓律名师
First name Law, last name Yer.
你的人脉肯定很广
Must be pretty damn connected
来辩护你的律师你自己都不认识
to get a lawyer and not even know who she is.
会员自然有特权
Membership has its privileges.
他保你出来了
He sprung you?
你觉得这很好笑  是不是
You think this is funny, don't you?
你早就设计好了吧
You got this all figured out, huh?
不
No...
其实我也不清楚
Actually, I don't.
响尾蛇为什么雇新人
When did Diamondback bring in new hires?
在俱乐部那件事后  他需要做点改变
Well, after the club, he had to change things up.
招募些新面孔
Recruit some new faces.
我打赌你被关起来的时候
I bet while you were inside,
条子们也试图招募你来着
cops tried to do some recruiting of their own.
永远不许质疑我的忠诚
Don't ever question my loyalty.
他在楼上吗
The man upstairs?
你问题还真多
You are just full of questions.
事实上
Matter of fact...
我们去顶层
Let's go to the penthouse.
我只是照吩咐办事
I was just following orders!
你就他妈是个傀儡
You're a goddamn puppet.
是谁吩咐你的
Who gave you the order?
是谁
Who?
是响尾蛇
Diamondback!
你忘了自己的位置了  问了太多问题
You stopped playing your position. Asked too many questions.
响尾蛇说得把你处理掉
Diamondback said you needed to be dealt with.
罗密欧肯定会以你为耻
Romeo would be ashamed of you.
你真令人失望
You're such a disappointment.
你是今天第二个这么对我说的人
You're the second person who told me that today.
我自有担当  沙兹
I'm my own man, Shades.
你自己去对他说吧
Tell him yourself.
赞
Nice.
抱歉  罗密欧  我不得不干掉他
Sorry, Romeo... He had to go.
幸好她朋友莱斯利知道她在哪
It's a good thing her friend Leslie knew where she was.
我很高兴你找到了那座公园
I'm glad you found the park.
她现在在哪
So where is she now?
她和奈特警探一起离开了
She left with Detective Knight.
路况一糟我就跟丢了她
Traffic got thick and I lost them.
抱歉  我不习惯做这种事
I'm sorry. I'm not used to doing anything like this.
我们会再找到她的
We'll find her again.
知道她不值得信任已经很有帮助了
Just knowing that she can't be trusted is helpful.
你做得很好  亚历克斯
You did a good job, Alex.
我就靠你了
Hey, you're my rock!
晚点见
Later.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
那可不是和商业伙伴该有的说话方式
That's no way to speak to a business partner.
你对我的俱乐部做出那种事
After what you did to my club,
你真的认为我还会与你同流合污吗
do you really think I'm gonna shuck and jive with you?
你最好改善一下态度
You might wanna check your attitude.
如果你不能为我所用
If you're not of any use to me,
那你对所有人而言都没用了
then you're not useful to anyone.
沙兹可以证明  如果他还活着的话
Shades would tell you, if he was still alive.
你到底在说些什么
What the hell are you talking about?
我不得不处理掉他
I had to let him go.
现在  我给你个机会向我证明你的立场
So now, I'm giving you the chance to tell me where you stand.
我除掉了沙兹和达蒙·布恩
I've taken Shades and Damon Boone off the table
好让你展开手脚
so you can grow.
我不希望我们也分道扬镳
I'd hate for us to part, too.
我本来也不怎么喜欢沙兹
I wasn't particularly fond of Shades...
而达蒙·布恩的死  虽说不必要
and the death of Damon Boone, although unnecessary,
我仍很感激
was appreciated.
但你需要明白这点
But you need to know this.
我退出政治游戏了
I'm out of the political game.
我的全部精力都放在哈莱姆天堂因上
I'm focusing on Harlem's Paradise.
用它作为
Using it for a...
促进社区关系的基地
a power base for community relations.
这一招英明
That's a smart move.
但你也使过不少昏招
But you've made some dumb ones also.
你永远不该在开放线路上谈起谋杀案
You should never talk about murder on an open line.
打开它
Open it.
种子基金  给你的新哈莱姆复兴计划
Seed money... for your New Harlem Renaissance project
并且翻修酒吧
and refurbishing the club.
我很抱歉
My apologies.
你的捐赠很慷慨
It's a very generous donation...
但世上没有免费的午餐
but nothing in this world is free.
你说得对
You're right.
我唯一的要求就是忠心耿耿
My only condition is loyalty.
跟随我  你可以随心所欲地重建哈莱姆
Stick with me and Harlem will be remade in your own image.
以后的日子都是我们的
We'll be doing this for years to come.
我已经控制整个哈莱姆了
Harlem is already in my image.
你要留下吗
You staying?
我解决了卡尔我就会消失的
Once I'm finished with Carl, I'll evaporate.
但是不要担心
But don't worry.
你偶尔会还会感觉到阵阵凉意
You'll still feel the occasional cool breeze.
好梦  玛莉娅
Sweet dreams, Mariah.
你出卖了奇科
You ratted out Chico.
你让老爹被杀
You got Pop killed.
兄弟  字写在了墙上
Man, the writing was on the wall.
可能有人看到了  就像我一样
Somebody would have seen him. Might as well be me.
我怎么会知道托尼会朝理发店开枪
How was I supposed to know Tone was gonna shoot up the shop?
谁都知道老爹的店永远是净土
Whole damn world know Pop's was Switzerland. Forever.
我应该揍死你
I should crush you.
可是你不会的  你需要我
You won't, though. You need me.
响尾蛇在哪里
Where's Diamondback?
我不知道
I don't know--
我操
What the--
你还不说吗
You still stalling?
好吧
All right! All right!
他在哈莱姆河旁边的一个仓库里
He's at a warehouse by the Harlem River.
在145街旁边  好了吧
Near 145th, all right?
我告诉你需要信息了  把我放出来
I gave you what you wanted! Now let me out!
坐稳了  巴雷特
Sit tight, Mr. Barrett.
明天垃圾车会把你捡出来的
Trash pickup is tomorrow.
里面空气不错  还有吃的呢
You can breathe just fine. There's food in there, too.
你不能把我扔在这里
You can't leave me in here!
我孩子还要换尿布呢
There's baby diapers in here, man!
求你了
Come on!
看来你口味不如以前了
Looks like you downgraded.
我更喜欢俱乐部一点
I liked the club better.
我是一个需要自己的空间的人
I'm a man who needs his space.
空间充裕是好的
Space is a good thing.
尤其是你要杀人的时候
Especially when you come to kill a man.
有人干掉了奇普和他两个哥们儿
Someone did your boy Zip and his two homies.
这不是凯奇的作风
That's not Cage's style...
所以我猜沙兹不领你保释他的情啊
so I'm guessing Shades didn't appreciate you bailing him out.
多明戈  你知道当一只响尾蛇面临危险的时候
You know when a rattlesnake is at its most dangerous, Domingo?
被逼到绝路的时候
When it's cornered.
我要打爆你的脑袋
I'm gonna rip your head off!
"我就看见一匹苍白的马
"And behold a pale horse...
他骑在马上  他的名字叫做死亡"
and he that sat upon him, his name was death."
你真的需要一套安保系统
You really need a security system.
-你在等我吗  -没有
- You waiting for me? - No.
我打赌他跟你说我死了
I bet he told you I was dead.
响尾蛇找到过你  对吗
Diamondback got to you, didn't he?
不  他没有
No, he didn't.
你拿着枪干什么  你不会这样的
What are you doing with a gun? It's not you.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我给你带了点东西
I have something for you.
我猜
Figured...
你会喜欢的
you'd want this.
上面有你的指纹和康奈尔的血
Your prints... Cornell's blood.
那你就没有可以勒索我的东西了
Then you'll have nothing to blackmail me with.
我不需要了
I don't need it.
我们现在是盟友了
We're in this together now.
历尽千辛万苦我们终于能够合作
You and I have come a long way.
有的时候不经历风雨就
You know, sometimes you have to reach across the aisle
不能见彩虹
to get things done.
你是指卢克·凯奇吗
You're talking about Luke Cage?
我们两个人的想法真是接近的不可思议
It's incredible... how much you and I think alike.
我们还在战争中
We're at war.
现在  敌人的敌人就是朋友
And right now, the enemy of my enemy is my friend.
也许吧  但是这也说不准
Maybe. But it might not take.
你揍过他  还给了他超能力
You did beat his ass and give him his powers.
而且
And...
康奈尔的手下杀死了他爸爸
Cornell's flunky killed Pop.
你真的觉得他会加入
You think he really is gonna jump?
加入到我们的阵营吗
Just jump on our bandwagon?
当然
Absolutely.
因为我们有他最想要的东西
'Cause we have something that he wants more than anything.
他的过去
His old life.
一个洗刷冤屈的机会  就在这里
A chance to clear his name. Right here.
如果我们让卢克和响尾蛇自相残杀
If we send Luke after Diamondback and they kill each other...
问题就全部解决了
all of our problems are swept away.
不管谁赢了
No matter who wins.
也许结果会更好
Even better.
我就知道你会来的
I should've known you'd turn up.
这里他妈的发生了什么
What the hell happened here?
响尾蛇
Diamondback.
这个贱人
Sweet sister.
慢一点
Slow.
放松
Take it easy.
他用了什么武器
What did he use?
响尾蛇怎么做到的
How did Diamondback do that?
我从来没见过的武器
Something I've never seen before.
就连你也无法阻止他
Even you can't stop him.
这是刚拿到的照片
These just came in.
又是一堆被打得七荤八素的人
Elephant punches all over again.
这又是凯奇做的  对吧
That's gotta be Cage, right?
-喂  -你好  是我
- Hello? - Hey, it's me.
你们发现了多明戈吗
You guys find Domingo?
-发现了  -来见我
- Yeah. - Meet me.
在哪里
Where?
我应该为此谢谢你吗
Should I thank you for this?
所有的线索都指向了响尾蛇
All credit goes to Diamondback.
我不觉得我们能找到他
I don't suppose we'll find his body.
不过我们找到了奇普的尸体
We found Zip's, though,
还在一幢旧楼里找到另外两名同伙的尸体
and two other thugs in an old building.
被枪杀  就在他们接走你另一个伙计之后
Shot up. Right after they picked up your other boy.
沙兹
Shades.
你难道不厌倦眼睁睁看着他们逃走吗
Don't you ever get tired of people getting out?
是的
Yes.
你在这里不安全
Look, it's not safe for you to be here.
如果你找不到响尾蛇
If you don't find Diamondback--
那他就赢了  我将永远生活在地狱
Then he wins, and my life is forever a living hell.
我有什么能帮你的吗
Is there anything I can do?
看看特科知道什么
See what else Turk knows.
他在123街小巷的垃圾桶里
He's in a Dumpster in an alley on 123rd.
就在芒特奥利弗特教堂和那家店边上
Near Mount Olivet and the shop.
垃圾桶
A Dumpster?
就算我们能稳住响尾蛇
Even if we handle Diamondback...
他也不会原谅我们把水腹蛇的死嫁祸给他
he's not gonna forgive us for framing him for Cornell's death.
这个很容易搞定
We could hurdle that easy.
唯一知道酒吧里真相的人只有
The only people who know what really happened in the club
你和我
are you and me.
我下半辈子都会为那晚发生的事而后悔
I'll regret that night for the rest of my life.
你迫不得已
You did what you had to do.
你不该后悔
You shouldn't regret that.
你那天在酒吧干什么
What were you even doing at the club that night?
我是想去那里杀他的
I was going there to kill him.
你抢先了一步
You beat me to it.
康奈尔从来不需要我的政治资金
Cornell never needed my political money.
他从来没打算还
And he was never going to pay it back.
他只是想控制住我
He just wanted me in all the way.
你有什么打算
So what are you saying?
他在我身上看到...我这辈子都拒绝承认的东西
He saw things in me... that I avoided my whole life.
现在我要变成  他严重的那个我
Now I am becoming that person he always saw...
我一直否认的我
and I always denied.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
我准备好了  宝贝
I stay ready, baby.
我应该穿着外套  地狱真是冷极了
I should've kept my coat on. Hell just froze over.
-卢克·凯奇在哪  -我在这里
- Where's Luke Cage? - I'm right here.
-我们有问题  -我也是
- We have a problem. - So do I.
我没法决定要先干掉你们中的哪一个
I can't decide which one of you I'm gonna knock out first.
-响尾蛇在哪  -我不知道
- Where's Diamondback? - I don't know.
我们三个之间的和谈更为重要
The parley between the three of us is more important.
你还敢说这种话
You have the nerve to use that term?
在这里  老爹死的地方
Right here? Where Pop died?
说出响尾蛇的藏身地
Cough up Diamondback's location,
否则我就跟在海门一样碾碎你们
or I'll stomp you like we were back at Seagate.
卢克  冷静点  哥们
Luke, be cool, brother.
没人要碾碎别人
No one needs to stomp anyone.
老爹把这个地方称为瑞士有他的理由
Pops made this place Switzerland for a reason.
凯奇  我们有共同的敌人
Cage, we have a mutual enemy,
能扳倒他唯一的办法
and the only way to bring him down
就是我们齐心协力
is for us all to come together.
我绝对不会帮你的
There's no way I'm helping you.
我们是来讲和的
We came to offer you a truce.
作为帮你找到响尾蛇的交换
In exchange for helping you find Diamondback,
你放下跟我们之间的恩怨
you drop your beef with us.
你们俩嫁祸我杀人
You both framed me for murder.
你给我什么条件
There's nothing you can offer me
都没法一笔勾销
that's going to make me let that go.
你的自由呢
How about your freedom?
这里有能用来
Right here is everything you need
卢卡斯
这里有能用来
Right here is everything you need
证明响尾蛇陷害卡尔·卢卡斯的一切
to prove that Diamondback framed Carl Lucas.
就算免去了卡尔·卢卡斯的罪...
Even if Carl Lucas is exonerated...
卢克·凯奇现在正因杀害水腹蛇而被通缉
Luke Cage is now wanted for the murder of Cottonmouth.
我会告诉他们真相
I'll tell them the truth.
响尾蛇杀了康奈尔和达蒙·布恩
Diamondback killed Cornell and Damon Boone.
你就自由了
You'll go free.
怎么回事
What the hell is this?
玛莉娅·迪拉德  你因涉嫌
Mariah Dillard, you're under arrest
杀害康奈尔·斯托克斯而被捕了
for the murder of Cornell Stokes.
我不是叫你去找特科吗
I thought you said you were going after Turk?
你打电话来后我一直在追踪你
I've been tracking you since you called.
我可不会让你又这么消失
I wasn't going to let you just ghost me again.
沙兹  后退
Shades, back off!
米丝蒂  别开枪  我们能一起解决
Misty, stand down. We're working this out.
你现在跟他们合作了
Oh, so you workin' with them now?
-他知道响尾蛇在哪里  -我可没这么说
- He knows where Diamondback is. - I didn't say that.
不管你知道什么  埃尔南
Well, whatever you know, Hernan,
你应该跟大家一起分享
you should share it with the whole class.
我什么都不会告诉你的
I ain't telling you shit.
手榴弹
Grenade!
搞什么
What the hell?
设计师
这是什么让·保罗·高提耶风的衣服
What type of Jean Paul Gaultier shit is this?
你是冲锋皮条客吗
What are you, a pimp stormtrooper?
不  我是死亡天使
No, I'm the angel of death.
-你要他来这里见我们  -没有
- You told him to meet us here? - No.
该死  看看这位蟑螂埃尔南
Damn! Look at Hernan the cockroach.
你妈妈应该给你取名佩德罗
Your mama should have named you Pedro.
沙兹
Shades!
该死
God damn it!
我刚把这个地方修好
I just fixed this place up all perfect and shit!
你们能出去打吗
Y'all can't take this outside?
-不能  -不能
- No. - No!
好吧  我...就随便这么一说
All right, just... just sayin'.
-别让玛莉娅跑了  -不会的
- Don't let Mariah get away. - I won't.
揍扁他  卢克
Kick his ass, Luke.
你知道我待会会把他们全杀了吧
You know I'm gonna kill 'em all later, right?
你得先过我这一关
You have to get past me first.
我可不用过
Oh, I don't go past.
我直接打穿你
I go through.